let quiz = [
    {
        question: "What is the name of the painter of The Mona Lisa?",
        option: [
            "Rafaelo",
            "Schiele",
            "Leonardo",
            "Kandinsky",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "The painter Courbet had the name...",
        option: [
            "Édouard",
            "Gustave",
            "Turner",
            "Manet",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "What was Watteau’s name?",
        option: [
            "Louis",
            "Chagall",
            "Antoine",
            "Rubens",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question:
            "The first name of the painter Le Nain is:",
        option: [
            "Jean",
            "Rembrandt",
            "Louis",
            "Modigliani",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question:
            "What was Modigliani’s name?",
        option: [
            "Amedeo",
            "Eduardo",
            "Macke",
            "Canaletto",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "The painter Dufy has as a name...",
        option: ["Georges", "Gauguin", "Liebermann", "Raoul"],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "What’s Caillebotte’s name?",
        option: [
            "Antoine",
            "Gustave",
            "Botticelli",
            "Warhol",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question:
            "What was Pissaro’s name?",
        option: ["Camille", "Pablo", "Goya", "Dürer"],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "The name of the painter Seurat is...",
        option: ["Georges", "Fernand", "Michelange", "Caravaggio"],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "What’s Utrillo’s first name?",
        option: ["Maurizio", "Dali", "Monet", "Mauritius"],
        answer: 4,
    },
];